<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Paveways</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="new_user">New User?</string>
    <string name="signup_here">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="signin">Sign In</string>
    <string name="firstname">First Name</string>
    <string name="lastname">Last Name</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="phone_no">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="retype_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="already">Already a User?</string>
    <string name="already_sign_in">Already a User? Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="new_user_signup">New User? Sign Up</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="available_listing">Available Listings</string>
    <string name="listing">Listings</string>
    <string name="network_not_connected">Network error. PLease Check your Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="categories">Our Categories</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="feed">Feedback</string>
    <string name="network_error">Please check your Internet connection</string>
    <string name="you_have">You have</string>
    <string name="product_in_cart">in cart</string>
    <string name="fail_todeletecart">Failed to delete listing</string>
    <string name="fail_toeditcart">Failed to edit listing qty</string>
    <string name="fail_toplaceorder">Failed to place order</string>
    <string name="fail_toorderhistory">Failed to get order history</string>
    <string name="continue_tag">Continue</string>
    <string name="qty">Qty</string>

    <string name="Approved">approved</string>
    <string name="faqs">QSTN1:My order has never arrived\n
                        ANS1;Sorry for the delays.Please call us for help\n\n

                        QSTN2:My order arrived damaged\n
                        ANS2:Please email us and give more information about this \n\n

                        QSTN3:I would like to return my order\n
                        ANS3:We shall send our representatives to sort the issue</string>

    <string name="contact">Phone Number:0797667411\n
                                        0717565039\n\n

                            Email:ukulimapoultry@gmail.org\n
                                    jacqulinembogo@ukulimapoultry.com \n\n

                       </string>



    <string name="thanks">Thank You For Joining us</string>
    <string name="thankshop">Hurrah! You got this far!</string>
    <string name="your_request">Please Wait \n For Admin Approval</string>
    <string name="paynow">Please make your payment here. \n Kindly note that payment should be more than half of the total amount </string>

    <string name="paynow3">Make your payment here \n it should constitute shipping fee only</string>
    <string name="payments">Your payment is successful \n Please check your order details for updates </string>
    <string name="amounts">Amount</string>


    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="new_product">New Product</string>
    <string name="my_account">My Account</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>


    <string name="forgot_password">staff login</string>

    <string name="create_account">Create Account </string>

    <string name="submit">Submit</string>

    <string name="address">Address</string>

    <string name="new_products">New Products</string>
    <string name="best_selling">Best Selling</string>
    <string name="trending">Trending</string>
    <string name="conditional">Conditional</string>
    <string name="password_not_match">passwords do not match</string>

    <string name="failed_request">request failed</string>
    <string name="is_invalid">Invalid</string>



    <string name="otp_has_send">OTP has been sent to you phone number. </string>
    <string name="otp">OTP</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">Resend OTP</string>
    <string name="otp_not_match">OTP is incorrect</string>
    <string name="create_new_password">Create New Password </string>

    <string name="overview">Overview</string>

    <string name="review">Review</string>
    <string name="write_review">Write a Review</string>
    <string name="your_rating">Your Rating</string>
    <string name="review_summery">Summery</string>
    <string name="related_prod">Related Products</string>

    <string name="search_name">Search</string>
    <string name="instock">In Stock</string>
    <string name="outofstock">Out of Stock</string>

    <string name="postedby">Posted By </string>

    <string name="wishlist">Wishlist</string>

    <string name="county_prompt">Choose a county</string>

    <string-array name="county_arrays">
        <item>Mombasa</item>
        <item>Nairobi</item>
        <item>Kisumu</item>
        <item>Nyeri</item>
        <item>Meru</item>
        <item>Kiambu</item>
        <item>Embu</item>
        <item>Migori</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>


    <string name="add_to_cart">Successfully added into cart.</string>
    <string name="fail_add_to_cart"> Please try again</string>

    <string name="add_tag">Add</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="fail_toGetcart">Please try again</string>

    <string name="add_to_wishlist">Successfully Added into user wishlist</string>
    <string name="fail_add_to_wishlist">Please try again</string>
    <string name="delivery_date">Deliver in 3-4 Days</string>

    <string name="fail_togetwishlist">Please try again.</string>
    <string name="no_prod_into_cart">You do not have any product to purchase </string>

    <string name="prod_name">Product Name</string>
    <string name="price">Price</string>
    <string name="cart_subtotal">Cart Subtotal</string>
    <string name="shipping_fee">Shipping Fee</string>
    <string name="order_total">Order Total</string>
    <string name="place_order">Place Order</string>

    <string name="fail_toordersummery">Please try again.</string>

    <string name="billing_addrss">Billing Address</string>
    <string name="shipping_address">Shipping Address</string>
    <string name="add_address">ADD SHIPPING INFORMATION</string>

    <string name="country">Kenya</string>
    <string name="address_line1">Address 1</string>
    <string name="address_line2">Address 2(optional)</string>
    <string name="city">County</string>
    <string name="pincode">code</string>
    <string name="state">Town</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="save_continue">Save &amp; Continue</string>
    <string name="fail_toaddaddress">Please try again.</string>
    <string name="fail_togetaddress">Please try again.</string>

    <string name="select_address">Please select shipping address</string>

    <string name="cash_on_delivery">Cash On Delivery</string>
    <string name="paymentGateway">Instant Pay</string>
    <string name="ksh">Ksh</string>

    <string name="thankyou">Thank You</string>
    <string name="your_orderPlaced">Your Order Has \n Been Received</string>
    <string name="we_will_inform_you">We will  SMS you \n about your order info and delivery date.</string>
    <string name="continue_shipping">Continue Shopping</string>
    <string name="order_history">Listings Order History</string>
    <string name="lipanampesa">lipa Na Mpesa</string>
    <string name="view_details">View Details</string>
    <string name="pricetag">Price</string>
    <string name="orderid">Order Id</string>
    <string name="orderinformation">order information</string>
    <string name="select">Select payment option</string>
    <string name="failorder">transaction unsuccessful</string>

    <string name="orderinfo">Continue to make payment </string>
    <string name="pay">Make Payment  </string>
    <string name="amount">Enter amount  \n payment should be at least 50% of the total amount</string>
    <string name="about">  About paveways</string>

    <string name="increment">+</string>
    <string name="decrement">-</string>
    <string name="display">1</string>
    <string name="addToCart">Add to Cart</string>
    <string name="viewCart">View Cart</string>
    <string name="units">Available Units</string>
    <string name="rent_terms_and_conditions_content">
    <![CDATA[
        "By proceeding, you agree to the following terms and conditions: \n\n"

        "The app is for informational purposes only and does not guarantee the availability or accuracy of property listings.\n\n"

        "RENTAL DEPOSIT:\n\n"

        "The Tenant agrees to pay a rental deposit in the amount of [Amount in Words and Numbers] (the "Deposit") upon signing this Agreement.\n"
        "The Deposit shall be held by the Landlord as security for the Tenant's performance of all obligations and responsibilities as outlined in the lease agreement for the above-mentioned rental property."
        "A deposit of at least half of the total price must be made before proceeding with any further processes.\n\n"

        "USE OF DEPOSIT:\n\n"

        "The Deposit shall be held in a separate account and not mingled with the Landlord's personal funds. The Landlord reserves the right to use the Deposit for the following purposes:.\n"

        "a. Payment for any damages caused to the rental property, excluding normal wear and tear.\n"
        "b. Payment for any unpaid rent or other amounts due under the lease agreement.\n"
        "c. Payment for any cleaning, repairs, or maintenance required to restore the rental property to its original condition upon the Tenant's exit, excluding normal wear and tear.\n\n"

        "REFUND OF BALANCE:\n\n"

        "Upon the Tenant's exit from the rental property, the Landlord shall inspect the property to assess its condition.\n "
        "If there are no damages beyond normal wear and tear and all rent and other amounts due under the lease agreement have been paid in full, the Landlord shall refund the balance of the Deposit to the Tenant within [30 days] of the Tenant's departure from the property.\n"
        "The refund shall be made via [payment method, e.g., check, electronic transfer], using the Tenant's forwarding address as provided by the Tenant in writing.\n"

        Users are responsible for verifying the details and authenticity of property listings before making any rental decisions.\n\n
        The app is not liable for any transactions, disputes, or issues arising between property owners and renters.\n\n
        Users must comply with local laws, regulations, and rental agreements when using the app.\n\n
        The app may collect and use personal information as outlined in the Privacy Policy.\n\n
        The app reserves the right to modify or terminate its services without prior notice.\n\n
        Users are solely responsible for any actions taken using their account credentials.\n\n
        The app may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance user experience.\n\n

    By accepting these terms and conditions, you acknowledge that you have read and understood them.
    ]]>
</string>
    <string name="sale_terms_and_conditions_content">
    <![CDATA[
        "By proceeding, you agree to the following terms and conditions: \n\n"

        "The app is for informational purposes only and does not guarantee the availability or accuracy of property listings.\n\n"

        "A deposit of at least half of the total price must be made before proceeding with any further processes.\n"
        "A facilitation fee of Ksh 10,000 is required for all purchasing processes.\n\n"


        Users are responsible for verifying the details and authenticity of property listings before making any rental decisions.\n\n
        The app is not liable for any transactions, disputes, or issues arising between property owners and renters.\n\n
        Users must comply with local laws, regulations, and rental agreements when using the app.\n\n
        The app may collect and use personal information as outlined in the Privacy Policy.\n\n
        The app reserves the right to modify or terminate its services without prior notice.\n\n
        Users are solely responsible for any actions taken using their account credentials.\n\n
        The app may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance user experience.\n\n

    By accepting these terms and conditions, you acknowledge that you have read and understood them.
    ]]>
</string>
</resources>